(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025
WAK!
PEAFOWL OF THE BLUE FLAME
ANYA MELISSA
KOBO KANAERU
MOONA HOSHINOVA
KUREIJI OLLIE
TSUNOMAKI WATAME
TAKANASHI KIARA
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
IIDA POCHI.
PEAFOWL OF THE BLUE FLAME
KiLLKiSS
弄られば手垂れ流す
Fiddled with, letting it flow out
音のない音は招く
Soundless sounds beckon
名前を捨てたのね
You've discarded your name, haven't you?
あなたのモザイクが泣いてる
Your mosaic is weeping
can not, can not, no deny
紛れもなく真実
Unmistakably the truth
さあ 預けて
Now, entrust it to me,
回帰するように
as if returning to the source
エネルギーはサイクル そういまは
Energy is a cycle, yes, right now
無重力 象徴的なパレード
Weightlessness, a symbolic parade
この月夜に 仰げば仰げ
On this moonlit night, look up, look up
completeness
鳴呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, raise high the light of life
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy 欺いて
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy, deceive me
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy, hold me tight
ねえ無防備だね 美しい戯れに
Hey, you're defenseless; in this beautiful play,
人は壊れてゆく
people begin to break
'cuz we're all alone
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even after clenching your teeth,
手を挙げ 希え
Raise your hands and wish
oh, when you bleed, 惑星に沿う その影を伸ばせ
oh, when you bleed, following the planet, extend that shadow
ねえ私の世界が知りたがっているわさ
Hey, my world is curious to know
you bleed, yes, bleed その血で
you bleed, yes, bleed, with that blood
天の五線譜を書き換えれば
if you rewrite the heavenly staff
code 'KiLLKiSS' uh,
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy 欺いて
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy, deceive me
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy KiLLKiSS judy, hold me tight
ねえ無垢な様ね 醜い終局に
Hey, you look innocent; in this ugly end,
すべてが変わってゆく
everything starts to change
儚いのね
How fleeting it is
そうこのまま 壊れて
Just like this, let it break
CR詠ZY
Break away, break away 細胞レベル I don't need 不穏な現状
Break away, break away, at the cellular level, I don't need this unsettling status quo
出てる姿仕草滑稽でしょう Don't you think? Don't you think?
Your appearance and gestures are comical, aren't they? Don't you think? Don't you think?
I'm so lazy 多分そう Fine sound 並べてるだけの人
I'm so lazy, probably; just a person lining up fine sounds
Trash, trash, toss away Don't you think? Don't you think?
In this world この頭には What a beautiful 舞い散る花びら
In this world, in this head, what a beautiful scene of fluttering petals
Parallel like 呑みたいな
I want to drink it in, like a parallel world
Hey! 誰もが die die C-R-A-Z-Y
Hey! Everyone dies, dies, C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に Ride on Ride on Ride on Ride on
Ride on this fleeting emotion, Ride on, Ride on, Ride on
心は 95 狂気のサムライ
My heart is at 95, a samurai of madness
血走らせた目で 引くくらい Ready to die
With bloodshot eyes, I'm ready to die, enough to make you recoil
Hey! 陽は昇り あなたの空 真っ黒な空
Hey! The sun rises; your sky, a pitch-black sky
荒々しく引き千切って
Tear it away violently
ほら その場所で 聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Look, in that place, you can hear the mechanism of the heartbeat
轟くのは己の調べ 誰かのじゃない 己の調べ
What thunders is my own melody; not anyone else's, but my own melody
目の前に
Right before my eyes
広がる世界はブルー
The world spreading out is blue
ひとまず
For now
さあ MOVE MOVE
Come on, MOVE MOVE
Speak about 生き方
Speak about our way of life
There's no need
何をそんなに張り切って偉そうに
Why are you acting so high and mighty?
Give me more 愛を
Give me more love
右も左も
On the right and left
知りもしないで笑いだ...
Laughing without even knowing...
Don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
A shadow grins and laughs
Hey!
世界は大体
The world is mostly
CRaZY
繰り返すように
As if repeating
Ride on, Ride on, Ride on, Ride on
Hey!
わかってもいない
Not even understanding
あれこれAuthorize
Authorizing this and that
Tell me something for the new
偉大な希代な時代のバイブル
A great and rare bible of the era
Clap back
Losing my mind
Shooting my side
Save it
あなたのその瞬間
That moment of yours
Maybe nothing wrong
Nothing wrong
Lala, lala, lala, lala
Hey!
誰もが大体
Everyone is mostly
CRaZY
一瞬の感情に
On momentary emotions
Ride on, Ride on, Ride on, Ride on
Hey!
心は95
My heart is 95
狂気のサムライ
Madness samurai
血走らせた目で
With bloodshot eyes
Look alive, ready to die
ほら 陽は昇り
Look, the sun rises
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
In your sky, your pitch black sky
あらあら 引きちぎって
Oh my, tear it apart
ほら その場所で
Look, at that place
聞こえてくる 鼓動の仕掛け
You can hear the pulse's mechanism
驚くのはまだこれから
The real surprise is yet to come
まだこれから
Yet to come
あぁ 待ちわびて
Ah, tired of waiting
時計の針 ページを回し
Hands of the clock turning the page
猛々しく いざ Raise your voice
Boldly, now raise your voice
ほら すぐそこで
Look, right over there
始まり出す 孤高の宴
The lonely feast begins
奏でるのは 己の調べ
Playing one's own melody
唯一無二の 己の調べ
One-and-only own melody
わーい！
Yay!
Perhatian sang putri merak yang tertiup angin, aku Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID!
Attention, from the peacock princess blown by the wind, I'm Pavolia Reine from hololive ID!
Attention please, I'm Reine from hololive ID Generation 2!
皆様ごきげんよう、わたくしホロライブインドネシア2期生パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。
Greetings, everyone. I am Pavolia Reine from hololive Indonesia 2nd Generation.
And welcome to Pavolia Reine's Peafowl of the Blue Flame!
Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 Birthday! Welcome!
Yay! ようこそ！
Yay! Welcome!
えっと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして...
Um, there's a hashtag on the upper left...
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner.
It reads #ReineMEPtember2025, which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything, you can write it and I'll be looking forward to them.
ご感想 and everything, you guys can write!
Your thoughts and everything, you guys can write!
ちゃんぷるーちゃんぷるーで喋ってますけど、まぁそんな感じで。
I'm mixing languages here and there, but yeah, it's like that.
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now.
今じゃなくても大丈夫です。
It doesn't have to be right now.
But I will be waiting! Yeah, so just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage. Look at this! It's so cool, right?
There's a mysterious flame, mysterious locks, mysterious cans, mysterious...
Where's the liquid? Well, there was like a blue liquid there, but I mean you saw it, right? Yeah.
If you, um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know...
Usually you guys think of the color red, right? Automatically.
そうですね、あの火といえばですね、赤のイメージが強いかもしれませんが...
That's right, when you think of fire, you might have a strong image of red...
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Iya nggak sih?
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Right?
But actually, 実はですね、青い炎が一番強いと思います。
But actually, in fact, I think the blue flame is the strongest.
Yeah, so that's the theme of today's birthday.
I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through hot songs...
...and songs that will make you feel, aduh gerah banget, so atsui, so phew! gitu.
...and songs that will make you feel, oh man it's so hot, so hot, so phew! Like that.
Pokoknya, just look forward to it, okay?
Anyway, just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs we've sang today, we have two songs.
The first one was 'Kill Kiss'.
そうですね、すごく好きな曲で、阿部真央様の『Kill Kiss』です。
That's right, it's a song I really like, 'Kill Kiss' by Abe Mao.
そして2曲目は、私がすごい大好きなあのプロセカのユニット、Vivid BAD SQUAD様の『CRaZY』でした。
And the second song was 'CRaZY' by that Proseka unit I really love, Vivid BAD SQUAD.
And the second song was 'CRaZY' from a unit I really, really like from Proseka, by Vivid BAD SQUAD.
I hope you guys enjoyed it! Yay!
Emang kayak Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya.
Reine really, really likes the song.
Jadi masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs...
So there's still going to be more. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs...
...and I'm sure there's a lot of guests. I hope you guys are excited for them.
これからもね、もっともっと熱くなるからね。
It's going to get even hotter from here on out.
ゲストも many many many many many! So please look forward to it!
The guests are many many many many many! So please look forward to it!
But for now,
I'm gonna sing one of my original songs.
Do you guys know what it is?
The next song is...
Love Me Love Me.
Love Me Love Me
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: YUC'e
ずっと君の隣
Always by your side
じっと見てるばかり
Just staring at you
愛 愛 やまない雨
Love, love, the rain that never stops
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in this world
A H 潜むように
A H, as if hiding
そう 今 この手に取った
Yes, I've taken it in my hand now
痛みさえも愛の形
Even the pain is a form of love
運命に結ばれた
Tied by destiny
小指を握る
Holding your pinky finger
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
Love Me Love Me
私以外いらない
You don't need anyone but me
Love Me Love Me
君以外いらない
I don't need anyone but you
ギュッと抱きしめたら
If I hold you tight
きっと逃げられない
You surely won't be able to escape
チクタク 針が回る
Tick-tock, the hands turn
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in this world
G E S 交わすように
G E S, as if exchanging
感情 押し殺して
Suppressing my emotions
悲鳴さえも愛のメロディ
Even the screams are a melody of love
運命に結ばれた
Tied by destiny
小指を握る
Holding your pinky finger
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
Love Me Love Me
私以外いらない
You don't need anyone but me
Love Me Love Me
君以外いらない
I don't need anyone but you
愛して
Love me
愛され
Be loved
離れられない You & Me
Can't be separated, You & Me
二人きり Give me your love
Just the two of us, give me your love
願うほど
The more I wish
滴る愛の色
The color of love that trickles down
何もかも
Everything
全て知るまで Wow more
Until I know everything, Wow more
私以外いらない
You don't need anyone but me
Love Me Love Me
君以外いらない
I don't need anyone but you
Love Me Love Me
ファイアダンス
Lyrics, Music: DECO*27
Fire Dance
まぁ、こんなんでいいか
Well, I guess this is fine
はぁ、そろそろ病みそうよぉ、いや
Sigh, I feel like I'm about to get sick, no way
手抜き 手に入れた無理
Corner-cutting, I got the impossible
それを大事にすんな 胡麻の擂り
Don't treasure that, you flatterer
いつか来る
Someday it'll come
降格するかは今の自分次第
Whether you're demoted depends on your current self
やるだけやったね
You did what you could
誰かじゃなくて未来の自分に嫌われないように
Not for someone else, but so your future self doesn't hate you
切れてしまうの どっちだ
Which one will be cut off?
目の前 夢の壁 どっちだ
Is it the wall of dreams in front of me, which one?
勝手に理想 それで結構
Selfish ideals, that's fine
あとはひたすら前に進むだけ Yeah
After that, just keep moving forward, Yeah
馬鹿にされれば
If you're made fun of
耐えるほどに
The more you endure
叶えた時が 爽快だろ
It'll be refreshing when you achieve it, right?
まだ
Still
行けるはず
You should be able to go
まだ
Still
やれるはず
You should be able to do it
ヤバババナ
Ya-ba-ba-ba-na
ぶちかますバン
Let's go, bam!
さぁ 歌え 踊れ 騒げ 疲れがビビってんのか
Now sing, dance, make some noise! Is exhaustion scared of you?
ヤバババマ
Ya-ba-ba-ba-ma
ガッと忘れちゃい
Forget it all at once
邪魔で決めた限界なんて 冗談！ 喰っちゃっちゃ
Determined limits are in the way, No way! Eat them up
大体 そんな感じ
Mostly like that
いい子の安牌
Safe bet of a good child
ここで計画的犯行 必勝法
Here's a calculated crime, a winning strategy
音の鳴る方へ
Towards where the sound is
ヤバババナ
Ya-ba-ba-ba-na
ぶちかますバン
Let's go, bam!
さぁ 歌え 踊れ 騒げ あがれ まだまだ
Now sing, dance, make noise, rise up, more and more
Done, Done, Done, No!
まだまだ メラメラ
More and more, flare up
Ganan double mana, nanggo me ninit
Jas poin cho-jo-we, nani ga attatte ore wa ore
Jas poin cho-jo-we, no matter what, I am me
Dondon susumemiteru kōkai me
Keep moving forward, looking at the regret
Remix saseru kanga, honban tte yō!
Think about remixing, it's showtime!
ヤッパバナバナ ブン カマスバンナ
Yappa Bana Bana Boom, let's go!
さぁ 歌え 踊れ 騒げ すかびびってんのさ
Come on, sing, dance, make some noise! Are you scared?
ヤッパバナバナ ブン カマスバンナ
Yappa Bana Bana Boom, let's go!
かっとばせ場外！ 頭で決めた限界なんて
Blast it out of the park! The limits you set in your head...
当然逸脱 ちょっとパないフィール その感じ
...of course, break past them! A crazy feel, that sensation
いい笑顔の味 轟音響く方へ
The taste of a good smile, toward where the roar echoes
ヤッパバナバナ ブン カマスバンナ
Yappa Bana Bana Boom, let's go!
さぁ 歌え 踊れ 騒げ まだまだ足んねぇな！
Come on, sing, dance, make some noise! It's still not enough!
夜の始まりさ
It's the beginning of the night
バニーガール 誘惑される
Bunny girl, being seduced
不意に弾け飛ぶ
Suddenly bursting out
奔放に愛を乾杯
Toasting to love freely
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell you
恋の始まりさ
It's the beginning of love
バニーガール 誘惑される
Bunny girl, being seduced
穿って澄んだ
Piercing and clear
君の目を 離さないで
Don't look away from your eyes
さぁ 刻むステップ刻んで
Now, let's keep the steps
仕事帰りの疲れは
The exhaustion after work
私とこのグラスに
Into this glass with me
そりゃ自分好みに変えて
Well, change it to your liking
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings towards the world
私に注いでみない？ Oh
Why don't you pour them into me? Oh
ありきたりなラブソングでも
Even if it's a cliché love song
愛が込められてるの
It's filled with love
それでも汚れるのって
Even so, getting dirty...
君を見れば分かるの
...I can tell by looking at you
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down
無理矢理は 凝らさない
I won't force you to focus
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて ほら
So don't look like that, just reach out your hand, see?
夜の始まりさ
It's the beginning of the night
バニーガール 誘惑される
Bunny girl, being seduced
不意に弾け飛ぶ
Suddenly bursting out
奔放に愛を乾杯
Toasting to love freely
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell you
恋の始まりさ
It's the beginning of love
バニーガール じゃなかろう
Maybe not a bunny girl
穿って澄んだ
Piercing and clear
君の目を 離さないで
Don't look away from your eyes
君の愛を知った気でハイになっていて
Getting high on the thought of knowing your love
感動去っていて 毎度泣いていてさ
Emotion fading away, crying every time
そういう具合が良いんでしょう？
That's how it's supposed to be, right?
さぁ 刻むステップ刻んで
Now, let's keep the steps
君の顔色にまでは
Until the color of your face...
マシになってきてるから
...starts to look better
私をあげるわ
I'll give myself to you
バニーガール 誘惑される
Bunny girl, being seduced
不意に弾け飛ぶ
Suddenly bursting out
奔放に愛を乾杯
Toasting to love freely
伝えられてるはず
I'm sure it's being conveyed
夜の始まりさ
It's the beginning of the night
バニーガール じゃなかろう
Maybe not a bunny girl
穿って澄んだ
Piercing and clear
君の目を 離さないで
Don't look away from your eyes
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
ヤベェヤベェヤメェヤメェ
It's crazy, crazy, stop it, stop it
ホラ一丁
Come on, once more
ヤムヤムヤミ
Yum Yum Yummy
ヤミヤムヤミ
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Hylen
Yum Yum Yummy
本心本調子なんだった？
What were my true feelings and condition?
徘徊曖昧シャットダウン
Roaming, ambiguous shutdown
幻奏のランウェイ
The runway of illusory performance
逃げ切りワンダー
The wonder of escaping
修正調整何回番？
How many turns for corrections and adjustments?
ムービングセーブタクシー
Moving save taxi
ひきこもりダーリンさ
I'm a shut-in darling
パパパパもっとずっとマイハンド
Pa-pa-pa-pa, more and more, my hand
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
衝動言動クライエスケープ
Impulse, behavior, cry escape
メロメロブーム 転がるゼンシン
Infatuated boom, the whole body rolling
サンダービーポ ヤムヤムジャスティス
Thunder bee-po, Yum Yum Justice
ワンチャン狙うジャックポット
Aiming for a one-shot jackpot
願望強欲煩悩 眩ませるカカカカカッ
Desire, greed, and passions, dazzling ka-ka-ka-ka
完成完成完成！お裾分け
Done, done, done! Sharing it with you
あずきずきパラッパ
Azuki-zuki Pa-ra-ppa
冷めないうちに
Before it gets cold
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
あずきずきパラッパ
Azuki-zuki Pa-ra-ppa
お味はいかが？
How does it taste?
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
足りないまだ足りないわ
Not enough, still not enough
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
脳内まだ足りないな
In my brain, it's still not enough
ビビビドゥ
Bi-bi-bi-do
最高にハイで更新中
Updating at an all-time high
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
パパパパもっとずっとマイハンド
Pa-pa-pa-pa, more and more, my hand
嗜好の味あじわえ
Savor the taste of your preferences
駆け足ロマスピ
At a fast-paced Roma-spi
右か左か
Right or left?
逃げるが先だ
Fleeing comes first
ドチュドチュドクター
Do-chu do-chu doctor
空空のダンスホール
The hollow dance hall
タマゴウサギだ
It's an egg rabbit
ピースは揃った
The pieces are all here
さあベイビーベイビーベイビー
Come on, baby, baby, baby
文字数がないわ
There's no more character count
ヤミヤムヤミ
Yum Yum Yummy
ヤミヤヤノヤミ
Yummy Yummy Yummy
ラリルラリルリス
Ra-ri-ru ra-ri-ru-ris
眩ませてるグラ
Dazzling glare
壊れる前に
Before it breaks
アドキドキパラッパ
A-doki-doki Pa-ra-ppa
ルージュをつけて
Putting on rouge
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
アドキドキパラッパ
A-doki-doki Pa-ra-ppa
シフクのリズム
A rhythm of bliss
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
足りないまだ足りないわ
Not enough, still not enough
ヤミヤムドゥ
Yummy Yummy Do
正解もう消えそうだ
The correct answer seems to be fading away
ビビビドゥ
Bi-bi-bi-do
こっち向いてよハニーデュー
Look this way, Honeydew
ヤミヤムヤミ
Yum Yum Yummy
パパパパもっとずっとマイハンド
Pa-pa-pa-pa, more and more, my hand
キャットラビング
Lyrics, Music: 香椎モミ
Cat Loving
Lyrics, Music: Kashii Momi
痛いことは嫌いですが
I hate painful things, but
君の手のひらは嫌いじゃない
I don't hate the palm of your hand
言葉は飴玉みたいに
Words are like candy
甘く広がってココロ満たす
Spreading sweetness and filling my heart
全然分かってない！
You don't understand at all!
「永遠」言う通り 完全に不感症じゃない？
Just as "eternity" implies, aren't you completely insensitive?
どこにいても？
No matter where I am?
あ、なんで聞いてない？
Ah, why aren't you listening?
元々あの子みたいに可愛くならなくちゃ
I've got to become cute like that girl from the start
愛は正味 そこはハメ
Love is essentially a trap
勿体無いのだって分からなくなる
I even lose track of what's a waste
曖昧また旅 趣味 ご褒美
Ambiguity, travels again, hobbies, rewards
もう安くなって遊ばれないように
So that I won't be cheapened and toyed with anymore
今日だって ちゃんと内緒の傷繕い
Even today, I'm properly mending my secret wounds
ニャン体 よじ込みするから
I'll curl my cat-like body in, so...
愛して
Love me
Everybody today is a rubbing day.
Get it, get it, this is my courtship.
Any, any, anytime's funny me.
Give me, give me, love me, my darling.
アイタイ間違いなんて みんな言う
Everyone says "I want to see you" is a mistake
取り憑かれてるって
That I'm possessed
ならこの胸で美しく
Then, if it's within this breast, beautifully...
締め付けるような切なさならば
...a tightening sort of sadness
選ぶ言葉と
The words I choose and
惑う指先
My wavering fingertips
崩せない横顔
That profile I can't break
私しか知らない
Only I know
あ、乱高下 ご機謙もしかして
Ah, violent fluctuations, your mood perhaps...
今日は優しく撫でてくれるのかな？
Will you pet me gently today?
君のそれが耐えられるの
The one who can withstand that part of you...
障害で私だけなんだよね
Is only me in this whole life, right?
あからさまに 体まさに
Obviously, my body is truly
もう病んで離れられないよね
Sick of it already, yet I can't leave, right?
そうだよね
That's right, isn't it?
感情は徐々に
Emotions, gradually
歌声は徐々に
Voices, gradually
蒙昧末路のように
Like a path of ignorance towards the end
どんなに愛でていればいい？
How much love should I give you?
柑橘の匂いだって、しなびるのが、だ。
Even the scent of citrus will eventually fade.
もう、殺して叱られるだけだし。
In the end, I'll just be killed and scolded anyway.
今日だって、ちゃんとお膝でおとなしく。
Today, too, I'll sit quietly on your lap.
にゃーって。お好きなように風邪を出して。
Saying "meow." Letting out a cold as you please.
「はい喜んで」
"Yes, gladly"
「あなた方のため」
"For all of your sakes"
「はい謹んで」
"Yes, most respectfully"
「あなた方のため」
"For all of your sakes"
差し伸びてきた手
A hand reached out
さながら正義仕立て
Just like a tailored sense of justice
嫌々で生き延びて
Surviving reluctantly
わからずやに盾
A shield against the stubborn
「はい喜んで、あなた方のために」
"Yes, gladly, for all of your sakes"
「出来うることなら出来るとこまで」
"As much as possible, as far as I can go"
あと一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
奈落音奏でろ トゥントゥントゥン
Play the sound of the abyss: Tun tun tun
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス トントントンツツトントントン
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares: Ton ton ton tsu tsu ton ton ton
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it out more
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it out more
慣らせ君の病の街を ドン、ドン
Get used to your town of illness, Don, don
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドン、ドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, Don, don
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを ドン、ドン
Toss aside those supermen of justice, Don, don
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス トントントンツツトントントン
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares: Ton ton ton tsu tsu ton ton ton
怒り抱いても
Even if you hold anger
優しさが勝つあなたの
Kindness will prevail within you
欠けたとこが希望
Those missing pieces are your hope
Save this game, Mr. A
救われたのは僕のうちの1人で
I'm just one of those who were saved
あと一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
奈落音奏でろ トゥントゥントゥン
Play the sound of the abyss: Tun tun tun
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
分かれ道思うがまま Go To Earth
At the crossroads, just as you wish: Go To Earth
任せきりワガママな言葉
Selfish words left entirely to chance
奏でろハクナマタタの音は トントントンツツトントントン
Play the sound of Hakuna Matata: Ton ton ton tsu tsu ton ton ton
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it out more
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it out more
慣らせ君の病の街を ドン、ドン
Get used to your town of illness, Don, don
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドン、ドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, Don, don
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを ドン、ドン
Toss aside those supermen of justice, Don, don
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス トントントンツツトントントン
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares: Ton ton ton tsu tsu ton ton ton
はい喜んで あなた方のために
Yes, gladly, for all of your sakes
出来ることなら出来るとこまで
As much as possible, as far as I can go
はい謹んで あなた方のために
Yes, most respectfully, for all of your sakes
鳴らせ
Ring it out
3から6マス！トントントンツツトントントン
From 3 to 6 squares! Ton ton ton tsu tsu ton ton ton
読者の皆様、こんにちは。
Hello, dear readers.
お疲れ様です。アーニャ・メルフィッサです。イェーイ！
Good work today. I'm Anya Melfissa. Yay!
あ、ママ、ママが教えてもらった言葉で...
Ah, Mom... Using the words my mother taught me...
...お嬢様言葉で、自己紹介します。
...I will introduce myself in elegant lady-like speech.
皆様、ごきげんよう。私、パヴォリア・レイネ、あ、すいません。
Good day to you all. I am Pavolia Reine... ah, excuse me.
ごきげんよう、リセット、リセット。ごきげんよう、私、
Good day, reset, reset. Good day, I am,
ホロライブ・インドネシア2期生、パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。以後お見知りおきを。
from Hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen, Pavolia Reine. Please keep me in your favor from now on.
本物のお嬢様でございます。イェーイ！
A real high-born lady. Yay!
お嬢様ですね、完全に。
An elegant lady, through and through.
お嬢様配信。
High-born lady stream.
お嬢様ムービング。
High-born lady moving.
Is お嬢様ムービング。
Is elegant lady moving.
レイネちゃん、Selamat Ulang Tahun.
Reine-chan, Happy Birthday.
Happy Birthday! おめでとう！
Happy Birthday! Congratulations!
さっきは『バリ・ガール』を一緒に歌いました。
We just sang "Bali Girl" together.
いかがでしたでしょうか。イェーイ！
How did you all like it? Yay!
どうだった？踊れてた？
How was it? Did I dance well?
もう、腰が...
Man, my lower back...
マッサージ、マッサージ。肩、肩お願いします、肩。
Massage, massage. My shoulders, shoulders please.
あ〜ありがとうございます。これ、これ。
Ah~ thank you. That's the spot.
私もマッサージが欲しい！
I want a massage too!
はい、お客様、凝ってますね。
Yes, valued customer, you're quite stiff.
ここですか？こちらですか？
Is it here? Or this spot?
パーフェクトでございます。
It is perfect.
パーフェクト。
Perfect.
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Pochi-mama and Reine, No-Bunny Girl!
お嬢様ハイテンションで...
Ojou-sama is in such high spirits...
今日も素晴らしいです。さすがです。
She's wonderful today. As expected.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hari ini, today...
Today, today...
...apa namanya, gimana ya ngomongnya?
...what's it called, how should I say it?
Pochi-mama, did you guys see last time...
...Pochi-mama's 3D Ohirome?
...Pochi-mama's 3D showcase?
そう、二人で私の3Dお披露目でレイネちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました。
Right, the two of us sang and danced together at my 3D debut.
皆さん見ていただけましたでしょうか？
Did everyone get a chance to see it?
And because of that, today I invited Pochi-mama...
...to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Yay! Thank you so much for inviting. Arigatou.
Yay! Thank you so much for inviting. Thank you.
No, thank you, thank you. Thank you for coming. I had so much fun.
めっちゃ楽しい。ね、ね、ね。Jadi, apa ya, ngomongin apa ya?
It's so fun. Right? So, what should we talk about?
What should we talk about?
If I remember Pochi-mama, I remember Ojou-sama.
Because back then, I thought, gimana ya, I'm a princess.
Because back then, I thought, how should I say it, I'm a princess.
So I have to act like a princess.
Kayaku Ojou-sama dakara ano Nihongo de... apa sih Ojou-sama...
Because I'm like an Ojou-sama, in Japanese... what is it, Ojou-sama...
...ya Ojou-sama acting hitsuyou hitsuyou gitu guys.
...yeah, Ojou-sama acting is totally necessary, guys.
もうこれでパーフェクトです。
This is already perfect.
さっきの動きで。
With those movements earlier.
あのジャンプで。
With that jump.
OKです。こっち、こっち。
It's OK. This way, this way.
お嬢様。ホロライブIDお嬢様。
Ojou-sama. Hololive ID's Ojou-sama.
皆さんもお嬢様になりたい方はね、Contohしてください。
For those of you who want to be an Ojou-sama, please follow the example.
Contohって何ですか？
What is "Contoh"?
Contoh apa?
What example?
真似してください。
Please imitate me.
そう、こんな動きがお嬢様ですよ！
Yes, this kind of movement is what an Ojou-sama does!
本当にいいんですかね、これで？
Is this really okay?
ちなみに、あのネタバレになると思うんですが...
By the way, I think this might be a spoiler...
今日のグッズはね、誕生日グッズはね...
...but today's goods, the birthday goods...
Pochi-mamaが頑張りました！
...Pochi-mama worked really hard on them!
書かせていただきました。皆さんちゃんとグッズ紹介まで...
I was allowed to draw them. Everyone, until the goods reveal...
最後をしっかり見てくださいね。よろしくお願いします。
...please watch until the very end. Thank you.
Pokoknya, katanya jangan ke mana-mana guys.
Basically, she says don't go anywhere, guys.
Pokoknya tunggu sampai akhir karena ada goods dari Pochi-mama sensei.
Basically wait until the end for the goods from Pochi-mama sensei.
Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan kan? Makanya tonton sampai habis.
You don't want to miss it, right? So watch until the end.
Okay?
Ya gitu deh intinya.
Yeah, that's the gist of it.
Okay, kalau gitu, thank you Pochi-mama for coming!
Okay then, thank you Pochi-mama for coming!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
このあともライブが続くので、楽しんでね！
The live performance continues after this, so enjoy!
Yeah!
愛♡スクリーム!
Ai Scream!
教えて もっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about yourself
Tell me mo-mo-mo-mo, tell me mo-mo-mo-mo
聴かせて もっと あなたの声
Let me hear your voice more
Let me hear mo-mo-mo-mo, let me hear mo-mo-mo-mo
こんな時 ドキもうさえきれない
At times like this, I can't wait anymore
Oh I need you! Oh oh I need you!
友達卒業 運命の私に
Graduating from being friends, to the fated me
つけてほしいの
I want you to name me
勇気を出して
Gather your courage
見つめる作戦
The staring strategy
目と目が合えば
When our eyes meet
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah with this love, with this affection
目 目 目 とろけちゃうよ
Me me me, I'm melting
ね ね ね 気づいて my darling
Hey hey hey, notice me my darling
とろけ 大好き
Melting, I love you
Ice cream!
オリーちゃん！ハイ！
Ollie-chan! Here!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント！よりあなた！
Chocolate mint! But more than that, you!
こぼちゃん！ハイ！
Kobo-chan! Here!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバー！よりあなた！
Strawberry flavor! But more than that, you!
レイネちゃん！ハイ！
Reine-chan! Here!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリーム！よりあなた！
Cookie & Cream! But more than that, you!
みんな！ハイ！
Everyone! Here!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き！アイスクリーム！
Of course I love it! Ice cream!
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋 心愛で
This love is deep in my heart
目目ピカっちゃうよ
My eyes are sparkling
ねえねえねえ 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
とろけ 大好き
I'm melting, I love you so much
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
愛見つけて My Darling
Find love, my darling
愛気づいて My Darling
Notice the love, my darling
勇気を出して
Gather your courage
近づく作戦
Operation: Get Closer
手と手が触れて
Our hands touch
So... 止められない
So... I can't stop
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋 心愛で
This love is deep in my heart
目目ピカっちゃうよ
My eyes are sparkling
ねえねえねえ 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
それは あなた
It's you
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
さあアイマスケリーム！
Come on, Ai Maskcream!
アイマスケリーム！
Ai Maskcream!
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
White swans, you see
見えないところでバタ足するんです
Paddle their feet where it can't be seen
本能に忠実 忠実
True to my instincts, so true
翻弄も重々承知
I'm fully aware I'm being toyed with
前途洋々だし
But the future looks bright
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
So that's why I take breaks sometimes
この目でしっかり見定めて 行き先 秩序お構いなしで
Looking ahead with these eyes, regardless of order or destination
近道あればそれが王道 省ける翼あれば上等
A shortcut is the royal road; wings that skip steps are superior
ヤバ 爪割れた
Oh no, my nail broke
グルーで補修した
I fixed it with some glue
それだけで 完璧な世界
With just that, the world is perfect
大事なのは自分 可愛がること
The important thing is to pamper yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love anyone else
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう
A clever hawk, you see
見えないところにピック隠すんです
Hides its pick where it can't be seen
想像に一生懸命
Working hard on my imagination
現実は絶体絶命
But reality is a desperate situation
発展途上だし
I'm still a work in progress
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
So that's why I suddenly go out of pitch
その目に映らないだけだって やる気はメーター振り切っていて
It's just that you can't see it; my motivation is off the charts
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Dreaming with all my might, then sleeping with all my might
ヤバ 痩せすぎた？
Oh no, did I lose too much weight?
調子乗ってみた
I got a bit carried away
それだけで 選んでハイポーション
Just for that, I'll pick a Hi-Potion
付け足すに目標
Adding more goals
過少修正して
With a minor adjustment
執念に臨機応変千変万化
Adapting with tenacity through infinite changes
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう
Peafowls, you see
…バタ足するんです
...we're kicking hard underwater.
業放は邁進 迷信
Karma release is a headlong superstition.
感情は喪心 励心
Emotions are absent-minded, yet encouraging.
誘惑は脱身 邁進
Temptation is to escape and forge ahead.
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why my will gets broken so easily.
やっぱまさか at point
As expected, at point...
嫌気切り上げ
...finishing off my reluctance.
それだけが my tendency no count
That's just my tendency, no count.
大事なのは自分
What's important is to...
認めていくこと
...acknowledge yourself.
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
If you don't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
because the truth is, I'm crazy.
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Like swans, we're kicking hard where you can't see.
本能に忠順 忠実
Docile and faithful to my instincts.
本望も重々承知
Fully aware of my true desires.
前頭葉ようらし
It's for the prefrontal cortex.
だからたまに休憩するんです
So, I take a break once in a while.
ワーイ！ Gimana? How was it?
Yay! How was it? How was it?
Wasn't the gondola and the bazooka and everything very cool?
We've had so many songs, but there's still more!
Here's the long-awaited... (drumroll)
Goods Showcase!
今回も生誕グッズが出まーす！ Yeah!
Birthday goods are coming out this time too! Yeah!
まずはこちらですね、青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット。
First up is this, the Peafowl of the Blue Flame rubber mat.
E... Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat.
Um... Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat.
Ini seperti dijanjikan ya, just like how we said earlier...
This is as promised, just like how we said earlier...
Totally not a spoiler! Made by Pochi-mama.
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mat slash desk mat, and so we have another one!
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat, well, here's...
...ada lagi, beda, it's different! Yeah!
...another one, it's different, it's different! Yeah!
And along with that rubber mat, we have the tapestry! Yeah!
Ini kalian tidak tergoreng ya, kalian tidak tergoreng.
You guys aren't getting fried, you're not getting fried.
Ya apa lah kegoreng dikit pokoknya keren.
Well, maybe a little fried, but it's cool anyway.
Ya sesuai tema live dari kali ini,
According to the theme of this live,
we have 青い炎の孔雀タペストリー。
we have the Peafowl of the Blue Flame tapestry.
画像は同じだけど今回はエディションタペストリーや、作られたポチママも。
The image is the same, but it's the tapestry edition, also made by Pochi-mama.
Silakan dicek out, silakan dicek out.
Please check it out, please check it out.
だ、続いてはこちらですね。
And next is this one.
Mana nih lanjutannya? Buat kalian yang suka minimalis desain...
Where's the rest? For those of you who like minimalist designs...
For those of you who like designs that are more minimalist in nature, we have Blueming Flame Coaster!
We have 咲き誇る青い炎のコースター！ Yes!
We have Blooming Blue Flame Coaster! Yes!
And pokoknya temanya itu cocok banget sama tapestry-nya...
And anyway, the theme matches perfectly with the tapestry...
...dan juga rubber mat-nya yang tadi ya, ilustrasi Pochi-mama.
...and the rubber mat from before, Pochi-mama's illustration.
Jadi mendingan masukkan ke keranjang sekarang juga.
So you'd better add it to your cart right now.
Eh belum bisa ya? Ya udahlah nggak apa-apa.
Oh, you can't yet? Well, that's okay then.
And then next one, さらにこちら！
And then the next one, furthermore this!
Ada juga seperti biasa ada voice.
There's also, as usual, a voice pack.
Kali ini karena Reine suka sekali sushi, because I love sushi so much, sushi daisuki Reine ga...
This time, because Reine loves sushi so much, because I love sushi so much, sushi-loving Reine...
...membuat シークレット寿司作戦 voice pack!
...made the Secret Sushi Strategy voice pack!
Untuk kalian yang suka sushi juga mungkin ya? Let's go!
For those of you who like sushi too, maybe? Let's go!
最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には...
Lastly, for those who purchase the full set...
Buat yang beli full set akan ada suuryou gentei de...
For those who buy the full set, there will be a limited quantity...
直筆メッセージと箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
...with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped replica signature postcard included.
Akan ada limited edition postcard yang ada message dan tanda tangan dari Reine juga.
There will be a limited edition postcard with a message and signature from Reine as well.
There's gonna be a limited edition postcard... buat yang beli... eh kok Indonesia lagi?
There's gonna be a limited edition postcard... for those who buy... wait, why Indonesian again?
For those people who buy the full set, let's go!
通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入り何と？ポストカードがついてきます。
The regular version comes with a foil-stamped replica signature and message... what? A postcard included.
Yang beli biasa juga akan ada postcard yang ada message dan sign ya. Okay!
Those who buy the regular version will also get a postcard with a message and signature. Okay!
And then next up, I'm gonna introduce my new song, sis.
Well, I don't know, this is my first...
First time doing this genre,
so I'm a bit shy.
It's a little bit different from what I usually sing,
so I hope you guys can,
you know, even if...
if it could resonate with you guys even for a little,
I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするの初めてでした。
It was my first time performing a song in this genre.
だからね、ちょっとシャイです。
So, I'm a little shy.
Yeah, well, basically, well, being placed in a box you don't exactly fit, it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know, it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you you.
And even if you're broken, it's fine.
And no one's else's opinions should change that.
とにかく、自分をありのままを愛していいよって曲です。
Anyway, it's a song about how it's okay to love yourself exactly as you are.
じゃ、これから準備するので待っててね。
Well, I'm going to get ready now, so please wait.
Please wait, 'cause I'm gonna prepare. I got a surprise.
Yay! Bye bye!
PAVOLIA REINE
MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Are you by any chance a MERAKyats
who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing
using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
(That's mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging
by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership-exclusive streams
in which we can have various talks, play games together,
and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is...
GUARANTEED!
SAFETY IS GUARANTEED
Welcome to the Royaltea
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Say things I never wanted to say
Up in arms who can please you
Liven day by day
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Rinse and repeat until it's Sunday
Hold it so frustrated,
you know I can't do it no more
I'll say
Now go down to the core
Hear you unite
Can't beat it down my door
Yell out scream and shout
but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much
but not enough to please your eyes
Your idea of ideal
that you're screaming in my hair
I'm just so broken yeah
Oh stop me
Oh I'll figure it out
Never never never gonna figure it out
You want me to know what I just don't know
Want me in a hurry and I'm here alone
Little did you know I'm just me let it go
Lock me inside a box of your perfection correction
Tearing me down am I what you like
Now don't tell me what to do what to say
what to think about everything
But did you ever say I'll say
Could this be and so bad
What's now the issue
I'll screw up again
Yell out scream and shout
but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much but not enough
to please your eyes
Your idea of ideal
that you're screaming in my hair
Broken... yeah...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Comfortable and pathetic
I like it that way, get it?
Brutal, just settle is never that simple
But I so want...
To meet your harsh criteria
Too bad I'm never gonna...
No, I'm never gonna fit
I'll never...
One, two, three!
Yell out, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now
I'm just too much but not enough to please your eye
Your idea of ideal that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken... yeah...
Hey! Hey! I'll stop me...
Hey! Hey! I'll never figure it out...
Oh, yeah...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Hey! Hey! Hey!
PAVOLIA REINE ORIGINAL SONG
Figure it Out / SONG & MV COMING SOON
GUESTS + ANNOUNCEMENT!
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025 / 9/9 20:00 WIB / 22:00 JST